sareesbazaar.com 2011-01-05

# Wedding bridal sarees, Salwar kameez, Embroidered sarees salwar kameez, Bridal wedding lehengas, Designer lehengas sarees, Traditional sarees lehngas from India, Indian Sarees, Fancy Sarees

We at Sareesbazaar Online Marketing Team recognize your right to confidentiality and are committed to protecting your privacy. We does not furnish any identifiable information at the individual level regarding its customers to any third party. The information you give to us is held with the utmost care and security. This information is collected primarily to ensure that we are able to fulfill your requirements and to deliver you a truly personalized shopping experience. When navigating our web site, personal information about you is not collected automatically or without your knowledge. 

We are also bound to cooperate fully should a situation arise where we are required by law or legal process to provide information about a customer. We may share non-personal, non-individual statistical or demographic information in aggregate form with our marketing partners, advertisers or other third-parties for research and advertising purposes. In other words, we will not tell our marketing partners that you purchased a specific product, but we may tell them how many customers purchased that product.

**How do we use "cookies"?** **  **

sareesbazaar.com's cookies do not contain any personally identifying information, but they do enable us to identify you in case you have visited us earlier and to store items in your shopping cart between visits. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent that. Even without a cookie, you can still use most of the features in our store, including placing items in your shopping cart and purchasing them.  
(Important: the information is only taken from what you have typed into the online forms and not from your Hard Disk).

We (Sareesbazaar) don’t make our customer uncomfortable by frequently sending mails regarding new schemes latest arrivals etc. We would be sending you mails only regarding your order details and any correspondence regarding your order only. At no point will your email id be furnished to any of our marketing associates or any third party.

**Security of Information**

When you place an order on sareesbazaar.com website for a product, we offer the use of a secure server. The Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encrypts all the information you input before it is sent to us. This prevents your personal data from being interpreted even if hacked while submitting it to our server. At the time of submitting your Credit Card details you will be redirected to a Highly Secure Payment server where Sareesbazaar its associates have no access to your information. Sareesbazaar always see to that your privacy is maintained at all time during your time of shopping at our eStore. We will not disclose any sort of personally identifiable information except when you give us requisite permission or under special circumstances such as when the law requires it. 

In summary Sareesbazaar always respect the privacy of our customers completely. We use the information we collect on the Store to enhance your overall shopping experience. We do not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others.

We recommend to our rutting customers for visit again our online eshop at
